# Nakul Gupta

Delhi, India



gnakul2001@gmail.com



+91-8802631740



linkedin.com/in/thenakulgupta

## **Summary**

I started my journey when I was 14 years old in year 2015. I am a dedicated and efficient Flutter, Full Stack, Android (Java/Kotlin) developer with 7+ years experience. Certified in both Frontend and Backend technologies. I started my journey from Android Java, PHP and MySQL for backend then moved to Laravel, Flutter, NodeJS, Python and Kotlin. Now I am comfortable on all these languages and learning new things daily.

Languages and Framework Known:

PHP

HTML

**CSS** 

JS

Java

Android Java

Android Kotlin

Flutter

Laravel

MySQL

NodeJS

Python

and many more on my list to learn...

## **Experience**



### Senior Product Developer

Q1 Business Solutions
Jun 2022 - Present (4 months +)

## Class Representative

Tecnia Institute of Advanced Studies
Jan 2021 - Present (1 year 9 months +)

## Fitness Club Coordinator

Tecnia Institute of Advanced Studies
Jul 2021 - Present (1 year 3 months +)

## Eco Club Coordinator

Tecnia Institute of Advanced Studies May 2021 - Present (1 year 5 months +)

### 🙀 Flutter & Web Developer

**Q1 Business Solutions** May 2022 - Jun 2022 (2 months)



### **IT Operation Intern**

ClearExam Apr 2022 - May 2022 (2 months)

#### Founder and CEO

Nakul Telestock (OPC) Private Limited Aug 2019 - Apr 2022 (2 years 9 months)



#### Full-stack Developer

Freelance May 2015 - Apr 2022 (7 years)

#### Head Student Coordinator (TechnoVision Event 2022)

Tecnia Institute of Advanced Studies Feb 2022 - Feb 2022 (1 month)

#### **Education**



## University of Michigan

Programming for Everybody (Getting Started with Python) Apr 2021 - Apr 2021 Programming for Everybody (Getting Started with Python)



#### Tecnia Institute Of Advanced Studies

**Bachelor of Computer Application** Aug 2020 - Mar 2023 Class Representative of Batch



## 📗 Jain Bharati Mrigavati Vidyalaya, Alipur, Delhi

68.8% in class 12, Business/Commerce, General Mar 2009 - Apr 2020 Student of Atal Tinkering Lab

#### **Licenses & Certifications**



#### 4.0 Tech 101 Certificate Certificate - iB Hubs

IHQVYE97ZI

Programming for Everybody (Getting Started with Python) - University of Michigan CSS (Foundation) - StudySection JavaScript Programming (Foundation) - StudySection Structured Query Language (SQL) (Foundation) - StudySection Advanced PHP - LinkedIn AUolHYkR8d2 ZSf4CBS5fBHmYVNL Training cum Internship on Web development - Oyesters Training 03ccff0d2e761669e8bbb29a8eaef6ca37c8a6360c54778910929a62a8efda3c Training cum Internship on Full Stack Web development - Oyesters Training 68fb116b8396fadc65c4f5c8609aaa98aae2e71301ff09a526cf40ec54bc3b8c 5 Days Campus Ready Program - Tecnia Institute of Advanced Studies **UST084** SAI Road To Tokyo 2020 Quiz - Sports Authority of India Cloud Computing - Careerera -SNVA EduTech 0000903357 **Python** - CETPA Infotech Pvt. Itd. Data Science - CETPA Infotech Pvt. ltd. Essay Compition (Eco Club) - Tecnia Institute of Advanced Studies Poster Making (Eco Club) - Tecnia Institute of Advanced Studies Fitness Quiz - Tecnia Institute of Advanced Studies Fitness Quiz - Tecnia Institute of Advanced Studies

**Aadhaar Hackathon 2021** - Unique Identification Authority of India (UIDAI)

- Office Automation (MS-Office) Tecnia Institute of Advanced Studies
  10025
- National Level Coding Competition Coding Blocks
- **G** Google IT Automation with Python Google
- Web Design for Everybody University of Michigan
- Sales and Marketing Intern Younity.in
- Learning Google Flutter for Mobile Developers LinkedIn AdZuf2B1gXnmP-q2rXXECZrB-zPm
- Java 8 Essential Training LinkedIn Ac1eniWkF31xpmulv\_KYZw\_oY7xU

#### **Skills**

flutter • Node.js • nodejs • Bootstrap • Css • AJAX • Start-up Ventures • Executive Management • CEOs • Social Media Optimization (SMO)